Waiting upon the Lord can be a sacred
place, a place of polishing
and refining where we can come to know
the Savior in a deeply personal way.
Waiting upon the Lord may also be a
place where we find ourselves
asking, "Oh, God, where art thou?" A
place where spiritual perseverance
requires us to exercise faith in Christ
by intentionally choosing Him again
and again and again.
I know this place and I understand this
type of waiting.
I spent countless hours at a cancer
treatment facility, united in my
suffering with many who were yearning to
be healed.
Some lived; others did not.
I learned in a profound way that
deliverance from our trials is
different for each of us, and therefore
our focus should be less
about the way in which we are delivered
and more about the Deliverer Himself.
Our emphasis should always be on Jesus
Christ.